Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on Trade Unions PE.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- U, 1832-2009; 7.5 Linear Feet in 7 record cartons and 1 manuscript box
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America: District Council of New York City and Vicinity: Pension Fund, 1963 (Box 40)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America: District Council of Suffolk County, 1962 (Box 40)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America: District Council of Syracuse, NY, 1904, undated (Box 40)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America: Fliers, 1990-2000, undated (Box 40)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America: Health and Safety Hazard Identification Program, undated (Box 40)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America: Local 34 (San Francisco, CA), undated (Box 40)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America: Local 101 (Baltimore, MD), undated (Box 40)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America: Local 376 (Brooklyn, NY), 1926 (Box 41)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America: Local 502 (Canandaigua, NY), 1900 (Box 41)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America: Local 608 (New York, NY), undated (Box 41)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America: Local 787 (Brooklyn, NY), 1975 (Box 41)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America: Local 1456 (Dockbuilders, Pier Carpenters, Shorers, House Movers, Pile Drivers, Divers, Tenders and Foundation and Marine Constructors, New York, NY), 1981 (Box 41)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America: Local 1780, 1967 (Box 41)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America: New York Carpenters for a Stronger Union, 1982-1990, undated (Box 41)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America: New York State Council, 1937 (Box 41)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America: Newspaper Clippings, Articles and Publications, 1940-2001, undated (Box 41)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America: Pamphlets and Publications, 1982-2000, undated (Box 41)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America: Pension Fund, 1961-1963 (Box 41)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America: Pension Fund, 1964, undated (Box 41)
  - United Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees and Railway Shop Laborers, 1919 (Box 41)
  - United Brotherhood of Tailors, 1913 (Box 41)
  - United Building Service and Domestic Workers Association of Brooklyn (Brooklyn, NY), undated (Box 41)
  - United Cannery, Agricultural, Packing and Allied Workers of America, 1937-1941, undated (Box 41)
  - United Carpenters and Joiners of Scotland, 1832 (Box 41)
  - United Cement, Lime, and Gypsum Workers International Union, 1937-1962 (Box 41, Box 49, Folder 22)
  - United Cement, Lime, and Gypsum Workers International Union, 1976-1980, undated (Box 41)
  - United Chocolate Workers of America, 1938-1939, undated (Box 41)
  - United Cloth Hat and Cap Makers of North America, 1906 (Box 41)
  - United Cloth Hat and Cap Makers of North America: Constitutions, 1901, 1913, undated (Box 41)
  - United Construction Workers Organizing Committee, 1940-1941 (Box 41)
  - United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America, 1944-1949 (Box 41)
  - United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America: Local 180, 1944 (Box 41)
  - United Farm Workers, 1965-1969, undated (Box 41, Box 49, Folder 23)
  - United Farm Workers, 1970-1972 (Box 41)
  - United Farm Workers I, 1973 (Box 41)
  - United Farm Workers II, 1973 (Box 41)
  - United Farm Workers, 1974 (Box 41)
  - United Farm Workers, 1975 (Box 41)
  - United Farm Workers, 1976 (Box 41)
  - United Farm Workers, 1977 (Box 41)
  - United Farm Workers, 1979 (Box 41)
  - United Farm Workers, 1980-1982 (Box 41)
  - United Farm Workers, 1985 (Box 41)
  - United Farm Workers, 1986-1987 (Box 41)
  - United Farm Workers, 1988-1989 (Box 41)
  - United Farm Workers, 1990-2000 (Box 41)
  - United Farm Workers I, undated (Box 41)
  - United Farm Workers II, undated (Box 41)
  - United Farm Workers III, undated (Box 41)
  - United Farm Workers IV, undated (Box 41)
  - United Farm Workers: Lettuce Boycott, 1972 (Box 41)
  - United Federal Workers of America, 1941-1950, undated (Box 42)
  - United Federal Workers of America: Local 21, 1945 (Box 42)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union, 1979 (Box 42)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union, 1980 (Box 42)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union, 1981-1997 (Box 42)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union, undated (Box 42)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union: Agreements (Various Locals), 1990-1996 (Box 42)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union: Joint Board Fur, Leather and Machine Workers' Unions, 1996 (Box 42)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union: Local 1, 1984-1985 (Box 42)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union: Local 174 I, 1986-1996 (Box 42)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union: Local 174 II, 1986-1996 (Box 42)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union: Local 342 (New York), 1984 (Box 42)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union: Local 881, undated (Box 42)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union: Local 888, 1990 (Box 42)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union: Local 1245 (Little Falls, NJ), 1990-1992 (Box 42)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union: Local 1518 (Retail Clerks Union), 1982 (Box 42)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union: Local 1529, undated (Box 42)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union: Local 1776, 2009 (Box 42)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union: Local P-9 I, 1985-1986 (Box 42)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union: Local P-9 II, 1985-1986 (Box 42)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union: Local P-9 III, 1985-1986 (Box 42)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union: Local P-9 IV, 1985-1986 (Box 42)
  - United Furniture Workers of America, 1941-1950 (Box 42)
  - United Furniture Workers of America, 1952-1957 (Box 42)
  - United Furniture Workers of America, undated (Box 42)
  - United Furniture Workers of America: Constitutions, 1939-1962 (Box 42)
  - United Furniture Workers of America: Local 140 (Bedding, Curtain and Drapery Workers Union) (New York, NY), 1970, undated (Box 42)
  - United Furniture Workers of America: Local 1010, 1958 (Box 42)
  - United Garment Workers of America, 1897-1936 (Box 42)
  - United Garment Workers of America: Constitutions, 1942-1982 (Box 42)
  - United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers of America, 1950-1952 (Box 42)
  - United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers of America: Local 121 (Chemical Workers Union), 1946 (Box 42)
  - United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers of America: Local 283, 1950 (Box 42)
  - United Glass and Ceramic Workers of North America, 1964-1982, undated (Box 42)
  - United Glass and Ceramic Workers of North America: Constitutions and By-Laws, 1954-1974 (Box 42)
  - United Glass and Ceramic Workers of North America: Department of Research and Education, undated (Box 42)
  - United Hebrew Trades, 1947-2004, undated (Box 42)
  - United Industrial Unions (Brooklyn, NY), 1943, 1958 (Box 42)
  - United Industry Workers: Local 424 (Bohemia, NY), 1986, undated (Box 42)
  - United Labor Committee of Massachusetts, undated (Box 42)
  - United Labor Committee (Philadelphia, PA), undated (Box 42)
  - United Labor Council, 1921 (Box 42)
  - United Leather Workers International Union, 1942 (Box 42)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America I, 1938-1943 (Box 42)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America II, 1938-1943 (Box 42)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America, 1944-1949 (Box 43)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America I, undated (Box 43)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America II, undated (Box 43)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America (Boston, MA), 1938-1946, undated (Box 43)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America: Constitutions, 1944-1948 (Box 43)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America: Legislative Department, 1940 (Box 43)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America: Local 1 (Magazine and Advertising Guild) (New York, NY), undated (Box 43)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America: Local 16 (New York, NY), 1940-1949, undated (Box 43)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America: Local 16 (New York, NY): Minimum Wage Arbitration, 1942 (Box 43)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America: Local 18 (Book and Magazine Guild) (New York, NY), 1940, 1949 (Box 43)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America: Local 41 (Industrial Insurance Agents Union) (Boston, MA), undated (Box 43)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America: Local 60, undated (Box 43)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America: Local 96 (Financial Employees Guild) (New York, NY), 1950 (Box 43)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America: Local 109 (Screen Office and Professional Employees Guild) (New York, NY), 1948, undated (Box 43)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America: Local 231 (Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians) (New York, NY), 1946-1947 (Box 43)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America: Merger, 1950, undated (Box 43)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America: New York Joint Council, 1939-1943, undated (Box 43)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America: Radio Guild, 1946 (Box 43)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America: West Coast Region, 1946 (Box 43)
  - United Packinghouse, Food and Allied Workers, 1963, undated (Box 43)
  - United Packinghouse Workers of America, 1945-1949 (Box 43)
  - United Packinghouse Workers of America, 1950 (Box 43)
  - United Packinghouse Workers of America, undated (Box 43)
  - United Packinghouse Workers of America: Constitutional Convention, 1944 (Box 43)
  - United Packinghouse Workers of America: Constitutional Convention, 1954 (Box 43)
  - United Packinghouse Workers of America: Constitutions, 1948-1962 (Box 43)
  - United Packinghouse Workers of America: Civil Rights, 1953, undated (Box 43)
  - United Packinghouse Workers of America: District 1: Social Services Program, 1968 (Box 43)
  - United Packinghouse Workers of America: Local 347 (Chicago, IL), 1939 (Box 43)
  - United Paper, Novelty and Toy Workers International Union, 1943 (Box 43)
  - United Papermakers and Paperworkers, 1960 (Box 43)
  - United Papermakers and Paperworkers International Union: Agreements, 1970-1971 (Box 43)
  - United Paperworkers International Union, 1975-1988 (Box 43)
  - United Paperworkers International Union, undated (Box 43)
  - United Paperworkers International Union: Constitutions, 1972, 1984 (Box 43)
  - United Paperworkers International Union: Local 14 (Jay, ME), undated (Box 43)
  - United Paperworkers International Union: Local 107, 1988 (Box 43)
  - United Paperworkers International Union: Local 6288, 1988, undated (Box 43)
  - United Paperworkers International Union: Local 7837 (Decatur, IL), 1994 (Box 43)
  - United Paperworkers International Union: Special Projects Department, undated (Box 43)
  - United Paperworkers of America, 1947-1950 (Box 43)
  - United Plant Guard Workers of America, 1961, 1970, 1975 (Box 43)
  - United Printed Book Binders: Number 1 of New York, 1891 (Box 43)
  - United Public and Service Employees (Durham, NC), undated (Box 43)
  - United Public Workers of America, 1947-1952, 1993 (Box 43)
  - United Public Workers of America, undated (Box 43)
  - United Public Workers of America: Conventions, 1946, 1948 (Box 44)
  - United Public Workers of America: Local 1 (New York, NY), 1949-1951, undated (Box 44)
  - United Public Workers of America: Local 20 (Federal Workers Union) (New York, NY), undated (Box 44)
  - United Public Workers of America: Local 713, undated (Box 44)
  - United Railroad Workers of America, 1947, 1954 (Box 44)
  - United Rank and File Painters of Greater New York, 1967 (Box 44)
  - United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, 1939 (Box 44)
  - United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America: Local 923 (United Culinary Employees of New York), undated (Box 44)
  - United Retail Employees of America, undated (Box 44)
  - United Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Employees of America, 1942-1946 (Box 44)
  - United Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Employees of America: Local 1S (New York, NY), 1945, undated (Box 44)
  - United Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Employees of America: Local 20 (Chicago, IL), 1944, undated (Box 44)
  - United Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Employees of America: Local 65, 1938-1945, undated (Box 44)
  - United Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Employees of America: Local 1250 (Brooklyn, NY), 1945, undated (Box 44)
  - United Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Employees of America: Pamphlet Labor Conditions in Bolivia, 1943 (Box 44)
  - United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1947-1954 (Box 44)
  - United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1956-1959 (Box 44)
  - United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1960-1965 (Box 44)
  - United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1971-1975 (Box 44)
  - United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, undated (Box 44)
  - United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America: Agreements, 1976 (Box 44)
  - United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America: Constitutions, 1946-1978 (Box 44)
  - United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America: Local 12 (East Gadsden, AL), 1981, undated (Box 44)
  - United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America: Local 93, undated (Box 44)
  - United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America: Local 621, undated (Box 44)
  - United Rubber Workers of America, 1936-1945, undated (Box 44)
  - United Rubber Workers of America: Constitutions, 1937-1941 (Box 44)
  - United Rubber Workers of America: Local 288, undated (Box 44)
  - United Rubber Workers of America: Local 350 (Chicago, IL), undated (Box 44)
  - United Scenic Artists Local 350 (Chicago, Il), undated (Box 44)
  - United Shoe Service Employees Union: Local 563 (Brooklyn, NY), undated (Box 44)
  - United Shoe Workers of America, undated (Box 44)
  - United Shoe Workers of America: Constitutions, 1937 (Box 44)
  - United Shoe Workers of America: Joint Council No. 13, 1950-1978, undated (Box 44)
  - United Shoe Workers of America: Local 54 (New York, NY), 1956, 1963 (Box 44)
  - United Shoe Workers of America: Local 563 (Brooklyn, NY), 1937 (Box 44)
  - United Slate, Tile and Composition Roofers, Damp and Waterproof Workers' Association, 1942, 1949 (Box 44)
  - United Stone and Allied Products Workers of America, 1941-1974 (Box 44)
  - United Telephone Organizations, 1940, undated (Box 44)
  - United Telephone Workers of Delaware, 1983 (Box 44)
  - United Textile Workers of America, 1934-1950 (Box 44)
  - United Textile Workers of America, 1973-1993, undated (Box 45)
  - United Textile Workers of America: Constitutions, 1936-1976 (Box 45)
  - United Textile Workers of America: Yarn Finishers Union, undated (Box 45)
  - United Trade Society of Journeymen Tailors in the City of New York: Bye-Laws [sic], 1833 (Box 45)
  - United Trade Unionists (Brooklyn, NY), 1975, undated (Box 45)
  - United Trades Union Congress, 1958-1960 (Box 45)
  - United Transport Service Employees of America, 1940-1943, undated (Box 45)
  - United Transportation Union, 1968-1988 (Box 45)
  - United Transportation Union, undated (Box 45)
  - United Transportation Union: Constitutions, 1974-1983, undated (Box 45)
  - United Transportation Union: Local 100 (Oakland, CA), 1979 (Box 45)
  - United Transportation Union: Local 1699, undated (Box 45)
  - United Union of Roofers, Waterprocters and Allied Workers, 1988 (Box 45)
  - United University Professions, 1974-1985 (Box 45)
  - United University Professions, 1988-1993 (Box 45)
  - United Utilities Union of America, undated (Box 45)
  - United Wall Paper Craftsmen and Workers of North America, 1938, 1941 (Box 45)
  - United Workers of America, 1932 (Box 45)
  - Universal Alliance of Diamond Workers, 1946 (Box 45)
  - Upholsterers' International Union of North America, 1957-1959, undated (Box 45)
  - Upholsterers' International Union of North America, 1956-1958 (Box 45)
  - Upholsterers' International Union of North America: General Laws, 1942-1960 (Box 45)
  - Upholsterers' International Union of North America: Local 44 (New York and Vicinity), 1928 (Box 45)
  - Utility Co-workers' Association, 1982 (Box 45)
  - Utility Workers Union of America, 1950-1979, undated (Box 45)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Consolidated Edison Company, 1958-1966 (Box 45)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Constitutional Conventions, 1954, 1965 (Box 45)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Constitutions, 1950-1987 (Box 45)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Constitutions, 1946-1965 (Box 45)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Constitutions, 1971-1995 (Box 45)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Constitution, 1999 (Box 45)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Decision of the Board of Arbitration, 1948 (Box 45)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Local 1-2, 1949-1996, undated (Box 45)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Local 1-2: Agreements and Contracts, 1946-1949 (Box 45)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Local 1-2: Agreements and Contracts, 1958-1965 (Box 45)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Local 1-2: Agreements and Contracts, 1968-1980 (Box 46)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Local 1-2: Agreements and Contracts, 1982 (Box 46)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Local 1-2: Bylaws, 1987-1999, undated (Box 46)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Local 1-2: Contracts, 1940-1962 (Box 46)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Local 1-2: Contracts, 1946-1955 (Box 46)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Local 1-2: Contracts, 1947-1950 (Box 46)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Local 1-2: Contracts, 1949-1961 (Box 46)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Local 1-2: Contracts, 1954-1955 (Box 46)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Local 1-2: Contracts, 1946 (Box 46)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Local 1-2: Contracts, 1953 (Box 46)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Local 1-2: Contracts, 1957-1959 (Box 46)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Local 1-2: Contracts, 1965-2004 (Box 46)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Local 1-2: Contracts, 1971-2002 (Box 46)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Local 1-2: Contracts, 1973-1983 (Box 46)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Local 1-2: Contracts, 1992-2006 (Box 46)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Local 1-2: Contracts, 2000 (Box 46)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Local 1-2: Contracts, 2000 (Box 46)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Local 3: Contracts, 1946-1948 (Box 46)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Local 3: Contracts, 1949-1950 (Box 46)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Local 4: Contracts, 1946-1949 (Box 46)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Local 4: Contracts, 1949-1955 (Box 46)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Local 4: Contracts, 1957-1959 (Box 46)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Local 7: Contracts, 1946-1949 (Box 46)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Local 223, 1960-1962 (Box 46)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Local 369, 1967 (Box 46)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Local 374, 1949 (Box 46)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Local 393, 1989 (Box 46)
- V, 1892-1966; 1 linear foot in 1 record carton
  - Variety Artistes' Federation (London, England), 1906 (Box 47)
  - Verbandes der Maler, Lackierer, Anstreicher, Tuncher und Weissbinder Deutschlands (Germany) I, 1925-1930, undated (Box 47)
  - Verbandes der Maler, Lackierer, Anstreicher, Tuncher und Weissbinder Deutschlands (Germany) II, 1925-1930, undated (Box 47)
  - Vienna Working-Women's Union, 1892 (Box 47)
  - Vietnam Federation of Trade Unions, 1966 (Box 47)
- W, 1847-2011; 2 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons
  - Walthamstow Trades and Labour Council (Great Britain), undated (Box 47)
  - Waterfront Employers Union of San Francisco, 1934 (Box 47)
  - Western Federation of Miners, 1904-1938, undated (Box 47)
  - White Rats Actors Union of North America, 1916 (Box 47)
  - Wilmington (Delaware) Central Labor Union, circa 1955 (Box 47)
  - Window Glass Cutters League of America (Columbus, OH), 1943, 1951 (Box 47)
  - Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union: Local 65, 1946 (Box 47)
  - Wholesale Dry Goods Workers Union, 1935 (Box 47)
  - Women's Trade Union League of Chicago, undated (Box 47)
  - Women's Trade Union League of New York I, 1913-1954 (Box 47)
  - Women's Trade Union League of New York II, 1906-1954 (Box 47)
  - Women's Trade Union League of New York: Annual Reports I, 1907-1951 (Box 47)
  - Women's Trade Union League of New York: Annual Reports II, 1907-1951 (Box 47)
  - Women's Trade Union League of New York: Conventions, 1922-1936 (Box 47)
  - Wood, Wire, and Metal Lathers' International Union, 1905-1911, 1939-1964 (Box 47)
  - Workers' International Industrial Union, 1918, undated (Box 47)
  - Workers Unemployed Union, undated (Box 47)
  - Working Men's Protective Union: Division II (Lowell, MA), 1847 (Box 47)
  - Workingmen's Federation of the State of New York, 1899, 1900 (Box 47)
  - World Federation of Teachers' Unions, circa 1953 (Box 47)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions, 2011- (Box 47)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): A.F.L., 1946 (Box 47)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): Affiliates, undated (Box 47)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): Allied Labor News, 1945-1947 (Box 47)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): Commemorative International Assembly: Leningrad, 1967 (Box 47)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): Conference (London; Paris; Budapest), 1945, 1950 (Box 47)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): Conference: Fight Against Monopolies, 1959-1965 (Box 47)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): Conference (West Berlin), 1961 (Box 47)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): Conference on Vocational Training (Turin, Italy), 1968 (Box 47)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): Conference (Illiteracy) (Nicosia, Cyprus), 1969 (Box 47)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): Congress Resolutions: Paris, 1945 (Box 47)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): Congress: Vienna, 1953 (Box 47)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): Congress: Decisions & Resolutions (Warsaw), 1965 (Box 47)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): Congress (Budapest), 1969 (Box 47)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): Congress (Bulgaria), 1973 (Box 47)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): Congress (Havana), 1982 (Box 47)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): Constitution: Draft, 1945 (Box 47)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): General Council (Prague), 1947 (Box 47)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): General Council (Peking; Sofia), 1960, 1966 (Box 48)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): General Council (Berlin; Moscow), 1968, 1970 (Box 48)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): Human Rights, 1963 (Box 48)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): International Bulletin, 1959-1960 (Box 48)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): Memoranda, 1952-1962, 1991 (Box 48)